{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": "VlKpEAYOH",
      "firstName": "Harry ",
      "lastName": "Potter",
      "emailId": "hpotter@csu.fullerton.edu",
      "phone": "657 123 4567",
      "password": "hpotter",
      "cwid": "8765432109",
      "streetAddress": "P.O. Box 279, 7334 Feugiat St",
      "city": "Santa Ana",
      "pincode": "99875",
      "country": "USA",
      "desc": "Harry James[60] Potter (b. 31 July 1980[1]) is a half-blood[2] wizard, and one of the most famous wizards of modern times. The only child and son of James and Lily Potter (née Evans), his parents served as members of the Order of the Phoenix at the height of the First Wizarding War until a prophecy naming either him or his future classmate Neville Longbottom the sole person able to stop Lord Voldemort's regime was made and overheard halfway by Lily's childhood best friend and then-Death Eater, Severus Snape. As a result, he was raised in Godric's Hollow, in a house protected by the Fidelius Charm for his and his parents' safety, only for their location to be divulged by its Secret-Keeper. In Voldemort's vain attempt to circumvent the prophecy, when the boy was only a year and three months old at the time, Harry witnessed the murder his parents as they tried to protect him, but an unsuccessful attempt to vanquish Harry led to Voldemort's first downfall, marking the end of the war and to Harry henceforth being known as the 'Boy Who Lived'",
      "isStudent": true
    },
    {
      "id": "w9FpYdUMz",
      "firstName": "Severus",
      "lastName": "Snape",
      "emailId": "ssnape@csu.fullerton.edu",
      "phone": "657 098 0987",
      "password": "ssnape",
      "cwid": "1234567890",
      "streetAddress": "P.O. Box 280, 7335 Feugiat St",
      "city": "Fullerton",
      "pincode": "94567",
      "country": "USA",
      "desc": "Professor Severus Snape (9 January, 1960[1] – 2 May, 1998[2]) was a half-blood[3] wizard serving as Potions Master (1981-1996), Defence Against the Dark Arts professor (1996-1997), and Headmaster (1997-1998) of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, as well as a member of the Order of the Phoenix and a Death Eater. His double life played a very important role in both of the Wizarding Wars against Voldemort. The only child and son of Muggle lowlife Tobias Snape and Gobstones witch Eileen Snape (née Prince), Severus was raised in the Muggle dwelling of Spinner's End, which was in close proximity to the home of the Evans family, though in a poorer area. He met Lily and Petunia Evans when he was nine, and fell deeply in love with Lily, becoming a close friend of hers.",
      "isStudent": false
    }
  ],
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": "NmpkrKouu",
      "timeLimit": 10,
      "topic": "Physics",
      "noOfQuestions": 10,
      "fromDate": "2017-12-12T14:30:00.000Z",
      "toDate": "2017-12-18T14:30:00.000Z",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the Father of Physics",
          "options": [
            "Isaac Newton",
            "Richard Feynman",
            "Marie Curie",
            "Stephen Hawking"
          ],
          "answer": "Isaac Newton"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Who was Born on March 14, 1879, Ulm, in Germany ?",
          "options": [
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Galileo Galilei",
            "Barry Barish",
            "Paul Dirac"
          ],
          "answer": "Albert Einstein"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "Who introduced Uncertainty principle ?",
          "options": [
            "Werner Heisenberg",
            "Rainer Weiss",
            "Max Planck",
            "Marie Curie"
          ],
          "answer": "Werner Heisenberg"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Who said \"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work.\" ?",
          "options": [
            "Thomas Edison",
            "William Fountain",
            "Madam D T",
            "Nikole Tesla"
          ],
          "answer": "Thomas Edison"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "Designed Cathode Ray vacuums Tube?",
          "options": [
            "J J Thomson",
            "Edison",
            "Newton",
            "Hawking"
          ],
          "answer": "J J Thomson"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Writer of \"Principles of Stellar Dynamics\" ?",
          "options": [
            "S. Chandrasekhar",
            "Kim Kom",
            "J J Thomson",
            "Madam Curie"
          ],
          "answer": "S. Chandrasekhar"
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "E = M * C * C",
          "options": [
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Isaac Newton",
            "Niels Bohr",
            "Richard Feynman"
          ],
          "answer": "Albert Einstein"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Former Lucasian Professor of Mathematics at the University of Cambridge? ",
          "options": [
            "Stephen Hawking",
            "Galileo Galilei",
            "Rainer Weiss",
            "Barry Barish"
          ],
          "answer": "Stephen Hawking"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "Educated at the Merchant Venturer's Secondary School, Bristol ?",
          "options": [
            "Paul Dirac",
            "Michael Faraday",
            "Max Planck",
            "Werner Heisenberg"
          ],
          "answer": "Paul Dirac"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": " Invented the first alternating current (AC) motor and developed AC generation and transmission technology ?",
          "options": [
            "Nikola Tesla",
            "James Clerk Maxwell",
            "Heinrich Hertz",
            "André-Marie Ampère"
          ],
          "answer": "Nikola Tesla"
        }
      ],
      "postedFor": [],
      "type": "MULTIPLE_CHOICES_ONE_ANSWER",
      "postedBy": "ssnape@csu.fullerton.edu",
      "postTime": 1512389111902,
      "reports": [
        3
      ]
    }
  ],
  "results": [
    {
      "id": "JcuoewAyH",
      "quizAttemped": "Physics",
      "quizId": "NmpkrKouu",
      "timeAttempedAt": "1512602369101",
      "result": [
        {
          "questionAnswered": "Who was the Father of Physics",
          "answer": "Isaac Newton",
          "correctAnswer": "Isaac Newton",
          "isCorrect": true
        },
        {
          "questionAnswered": "Who was Born on March 14, 1879, Ulm, in Germany ?",
          "answer": "Albert Einstein",
          "correctAnswer": "Paul Dirac",
          "isCorrect": false
        },
        {
          "questionAnswered": "Educated at the Merchant Venturer's Secondary School, Bristol ?",
          "answer": "Paul Dirac",
          "correctAnswer": "Max Planck",
          "isCorrect": false
        }
      ],
      "attempedBy": "hpotter@csu.fullerton.edu",
      "postedBy": "ssnape@csu.fullerton.edu"
    }
  ],
  "reports": [
    {
      "id": "6qc76UNjE",
      "reportedFor": "ssnape@csu.fullerton.edu",
      "topic": "Physics",
      "quizId": "NmpkrKouu",
      "question": "3",
      "reports": [
        {
          "reportedBy": "Harry  Potter",
          "comment": "Duplicate Options"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}